Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪♪♪
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[CROW CAWING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING
AND WINGS FLUTTERING]
♪♪♪
- [GROWLING, BARKING]
- [GASPS]
[GRUNTS, GASPING]
[PANTING]
Yes.
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
You failed.
I didn't.
The gun is in my hand.
I thought I had it.
Sorry, Father.
I'll make it next time.
Never take anything
for granted.
God will take it from you.
Is God bad?
God is fair.
[DOG WHINES]
PHOENIX: You almost got
me, didn't you, boy?
♪♪♪
Did I get my white hair from you
or from Mom?
From your mother.
I can't believe we don't have
any pictures of her.
Everything was destroyed
in the fire.
You know that.
I could only save you.
Was she beautiful?
She was smart.
Like you.
How many did I get?
All of them.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
So I get to go
to town today, right?
You failed survival.
It's been three months.
Plus, I just gave you
a killer haircut.
Trust me.
You need to pass
all your tests first.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS
INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO]
All right,
apart from the usual,
I have an order of
five ferns,
two ficuses,
and the Columnea grandiosa.
Gloriosa.
HERNANDEZ: Gloriosa.
Am I taking Phoenix today?
Not today.
It's been a while.
I said, no.
You either loosen up
that leash,
or sooner or later,
she's gonna bite it off.
[DOOR OPENS]
Go with Hernandez.
Back by sunset!
I will.
PHOENIX: Hey, Hernandez.
HERNANDEZ: Hey, gorgeous.
PHOENIX: ♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ All across the mighty sea ♪
♪ Sing, girl ♪
♪ Sing your little heart out
For me ♪
That's beautiful.
You made that up?
I think my mom sang it to me
when I was little.
That first part's
all I remember.
You wanna pay her a visit?
- But my father doesn't want me...
- I won't tell if you don't.
[DOOR CREAKS]
♪♪♪
♪ Fly, bird ♪
[DOOR THUMPS, CREAKS]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[FLOORBOARDS CREAK]
REPORTER: [ON TV] Police have issued a
statewide alert for Dr. Thomas Hanniman,
who's believed to be running
an organ trafficking ring
- in the Detroit area.
- MAN: Thank you.
The alarming number
of abductions
has recently risen in the city.
This is a developing story.
We'll update you
as more information
comes to light.
Now let's take a look
at the weekend forecast.
JERRY: [ON TV] Good morning, everyone.
I'm meteorologist Jerry...
[CHILDREN LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
BILLIE: Everyone, pull. Help me.
BOY 1: It's stuck.
♪♪♪
Hey, wanna try something?
BOY 2: Okay.
- PHOENIX: Do it.
- [BOY LAUGHS]
♪♪♪
- [ALL LAUGHING]
- BILLIE: Faster, faster.
PHOENIX: I'm getting dizzy.
[BELL RINGING]
WOMAN: Hey, guys. Come on in. Dinner.
BOY 2: But I don't wanna go inside.
BILLIE: Come on, guys!
PHOENIX: "Covenant Shelter."
BILLIE: Race you.
- BOY 1: Hey, wait up!
- [CAR HORN HONKS]
- You having fun?
- Mm-hm.
All right, let's go.
I need to pee.
Okay, well, be quick.
I don't wanna anger your father.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
PHOENIX: ♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ All across the mighty sea ♪
♪ Sing, girl ♪
♪ Sing your little heart out
For me ♪
[WATER RUNNING]
♪♪♪
Wow, you're pretty.
What's your name, gorgeous?
Mine's Raylan.
I don't care.
I need to go.
My father's waiting for me.
[DOG GROWLS]
[BARKS]
I snap my fingers
and he'll bite
your testicles off.
[SCOFFS]
Wow.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry if I scared you.
Who said you did?
I'll see you around.
Come on, Shadow.
♪♪♪
[VAN DOOR SLIDES CLOSED]
You okay?
PHOENIX: Yes.
Just a weirdo.
Yeah.
No shortage of those
around here.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Follow them.
PHOENIX: Thanks, Hernandez.
We had a lot of fun today.
I'll take her again next week
if you're okay with it.
No.
Today was enough.
- It's none of my business, but...
- You're right.
It's not.
You're a bad man.
A man who's done
terrible things.
At least, I know you think that.
Just like sometimes
I do about myself.
War changes us all.
No soul returns holy from it.
Don't make her pay for that.
Thanks.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SIGHS]
♪♪♪
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
- [SIGHS]
- [HORN HONKS]
[DOG BARKS]
[HONKS]
[ENGINE SHUTS OFF]
[BARKING, THEN GROWLS]
You mind moving your vehicle
off the road, please?
This is...
This is the only road
back to town.
You served?
Yeah.
We all did too.
- Iraq?
- Yeah.
Dishonorably discharged
from a dishonorable war.
I'd say that makes us
honorable somehow. Wouldn't you?
No.
Can you move your truck
off the road now?
Sure, baby.
Whatever you want.
[ENGINE REVS]
[BARKS]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [DOG BARKING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[PHONE BEEPING]
[GASPING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[HORN WAILING]
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR, THEN DOOR OPENS]
Lessons next month.
PHOENIX: Okay.
- I wanna go to school next year.
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- This is school...
- A real school,
with other kids like me.
Homeschool is safer.
I don't wanna be safe.
I wanna be normal.
I wanna have friends.
- I wanna live a...
- Enough!
Enough.
I already lost a daughter once.
I'm not losing you.
But I'm lonely.
You have no idea
what it is to be alone.
You have me.
You're not enough.
♪♪♪
- [RUSTLING]
- [BARKS SOFTLY]
[SNORTS]
[SHADOW GROWLS]
[SNIFFING, BARKS SOFTLY]
♪♪♪
[SNIFFING]
[GUNSHOT]
♪♪♪
"Covenant Shelter.
Your new home awaits you."
[SIGHS]
♪♪♪
[RATTLES]
Shadow?
[WHISTLES]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪♪♪
BLIND MAN: Shadow?
[BLIND MAN WHISTLES]
[STAIRS CREAKING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[LIGHT CLICKS ON]
[FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[DRAWERS OPEN, CLOSE]
[WATCH BEEPING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOORS OPENING]
[WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
[FOOTSTEPS]
- [DOOR RATTLES]
- [GASPS]
[CREAKS]
[CLATTERING UPSTAIRS]
♪♪♪
[FOOTSTEPS ON STAIRS]
[SNIFFING]
[WHISPERS]
Shadow.
[SOBS]
Oh, God.
[GASPS SOFTLY]
[GASPS]
♪♪♪
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SHUDDERING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GASPS]
[SHELL RATTLES ON FLOOR]
[YELLING]
[BONES CRACK]
[GROANING]
The box! Now!
[YELLS]
Go!
[PHOENIX SCREAMS]
[JIM-BOB GRUNTING]
Go get the girl.
♪♪♪
[GRUNTING]
Open the door.
- [GASPS]
- Open up!
[PANTING]
[HYPERVENTILATING]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[WINCES]
[GRUNTS]
♪♪♪
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
[SHOE SQUELCHES]
[GRUNTS, YELLS]
♪♪♪
[MUFFLED GROANING]
What the fuck?
Oh!
Hang on, brother.
Open your jaw.
- [MUFFLED MUMBLING]
- Stay still.
[MUFFLED GROAN]
[INHALING DEEPLY]
Breathe, brother.
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
The guy's a Navy SEAL.
[GASPS]
[COUGHING]
Fucking dead SEAL, bro.
♪♪♪
[GRUNTING]
[WATER HEATER SQUEAKS]
[PIPES RATTLING]
DUKE: Better get out of there, kid.
He's down there with you!
Blind fuck is down there!
- [SQUEAKS]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Call Raylan.
Metal box
is almost full of water.
You prefer
to see the kid alive...
you come in here.
You think I'm fucking with you?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
No.
There's a live wire
about to reach the water.
Come out, or she's fried!
[THUMP]
- [THUMP]
- [GUN COCKS]
[METAL CLANGS]
[GAS HISSING]
Clever fuck.
No guns, huh?
No problem.
[CLANKS]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [YELLS]
- [GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[GROANS]
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[BLIND MAN GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
[ELECTRICAL SPARKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
You're tough.
But you're done.
[HOUSE RUMBLES, RATTLING]
What the fuck?
- [VEHICLE APPROACHING]
- Yo, bro.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[DOG BARKS]
♪♪♪
[METAL RATTLING]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[SOBS]
- [COUGHING]
- Breathe.
Come on, breathe.
- [GASPING]
- Breathe.
Breathe.
- [GRUNTS]
- The old blind man did this?
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
[DOOR THUDS]
♪♪♪
PHOENIX: I can walk.
I said, I can walk.
[DOOR THUDS]
What's happening?
Cover the exits.
What the fuck?
♪♪♪
[SIGHS]
[HAMMER CLANGS]
They're still down here.
[RATTLING]
What's happening?
- Who are they?
- I don't know.
[GRUNTING]
RAYLAN: You don't need to be
afraid, little girl.
This has all just been
one big misunderstanding.
It's not me
you need to be scared of...
but the man
standing next to you.
Now, I don't know who he is.
But I know who he's not.
[RAYLAN CHUCKLES]
Should I tell her or you?
[YELLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
- Finish him, bro.
- [SHOTGUN RACKS]
No!
- Dad! Dad, wake up.
- Aren't you something?
[GRUNTING]
Let me go!
Come on.
No, it's okay.
Yeah, there you go.
There you go.
You really don't remember me,
do you?
Maybe this will help.
♪♪♪
See?
What...?
[SIGHS]
Years ago, there was
a fire in our house.
Cops blamed me.
I spent eight years in prison,
wondering if
I'd ever see you again.
I didn't even know
if you were dead or alive.
[SHADOW PANTING]
[WHINING]
- [SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
- This creep here must have...
found you
and kept you for himself.
REPORTER: [ON TV] Up next in local news,
a meth lab caught fire
in west Detroit this morning.
Police were able
to arrest the primary suspect.
The man was taken into custody
and could face charges
for a large number of crimes
committed
- over the past several years.
- RAYLAN: You have no idea
how much I've been waiting
for this moment.
♪♪♪
Did he hurt you?
But he did steal you
away from me,
and now he must die,
you understand?
Kill him.
- No.
- Fuck are you doing?
Not in front of my kid.
Do it outside.
Wake up, you blind fuck.
[GROANS]
Oh! Fuck!
[BLIND MAN GRUNTS
AND GLASS SHATTERS]
[GRUNTS]
Fucking coward.
♪♪♪
Take her to the truck
while I hunt this motherfucker.
Let's go.
- Let me go!
- What's wrong with you?
Fucking wanna go home?
[GRUNTS, YELLS]
[GROANS]
[GULPS, GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
[JARED GROANING SOFTLY]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
I don't care who you are.
I'm gonna teach you
some fucking manners, yo.
- You ungrateful, little bitch.
- [GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
[PANTING]
[YELLS]
[JARED SOBS, GASPS]
[COUGHS, GASPING]
JARED: No.
[YELLS]
Stop.
Please!
[SCREAMS]
Stop!
[GRUNTS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING OUTSIDE]
♪♪♪
RAYLAN: Move. Go, go.
Move. Now.
BLIND MAN: Move!
♪♪♪
RAYLAN: I'm sorry, man.
- He's back in the house.
- I know.
He wants us to follow him.
Enough of these silly games.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
JIM-BOB: It's his jacket.
- Attaboy.
- [SNIFFING]
Attaboy.
PHOENIX: Wait.
Stop.
Is it true?
Move.
What's my real name?
Get over here now!
When's my birthday?
- My real one?
- Stop it!
- No, you stop it!
- [DOG BARKS]
[GROWLING, BARKING]
- [GUN COCKS]
- [SNARLING]
- BLIND MAN: Go!
- [BARKING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[BARKING, GROWLING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
- [DOG GROWLING]
- [BLIND MAN YELLS]
♪♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey.
- [BARKING]
- [GASPS]
[GROWLING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [DOG SNARLING]
[BARKING, SNARLING]
[GUN COCKS]
[SOUND FADES OUT]
♪♪♪
[CLICKS]
[GRUNTS]
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[PHOENIX GASPS, SCREAMS]
Phoenix!
- [MUFFLED GRUNTING]
- Calm down, girl.
Calm down.
[BARKING]
- [GROWLING]
- [GRUNTS]
[STRAINS]
- [BARKING]
Stay.
[PANTING]
♪♪♪
Put her in the truck.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
- Your dog's in there.
- [SCOFFS] Dog's dead.
You don't know that.
You wanna go and find out?
[GRUNTS]
♪♪♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GLASS CRACKS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
No!
[DOG WHINES]
[DOG BARKING]
[WHINING]
[CLATTERING
AND DOG BARKING]
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[GRUNTS]
[CRIES OUT, GASPS]
[CRIES OUT]
- [SIZZLES]
- [GASPS]
- [FLOORBOARDS CREAKING]
[YELLS]
[GLASS CRACKING]
[GROANING]
♪♪♪
[EXPLOSION]
[SOBS]
♪♪♪
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
RAYLAN: Good morning, princess.
How you feeling?
You all right?
Wanna sit with me?
Come, sit with me. Come on.
Yeah.
There you go.
Door's open.
Not a prisoner anymore.
You mean, I can go?
If you want.
Or you can stay here
and find out
who you really are.
Do I have
any brothers or sisters?
Unfortunately, no.
When's my birthday?
February 20th.
What was my mother's name?
Josephine.
Do I look like her?
Yeah.
You do.
Tara.
That's your real name.
Everything that man
told you is a lie.
What happened to him?
He got what he deserved.
Hey. I'm not sorry.
You shouldn't be either.
I wanna go.
Where? Where you gonna go?
There's a shelter I know.
Like I said,
you're not a prisoner anymore.
♪♪♪
[MOTOR WHIRS]
[WHIRRING]
♪♪♪
WOMAN: ♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ Fly, bird ♪
♪ Out across the ♪
♪ Great wide sea ♪
♪ Sing, girl ♪
♪ Sing your little heart out
For me ♪
♪ Fly, bird ♪
[QUAVERING]
♪ Fly across the mighty cliffs ♪
♪ Sleep, girl ♪
[SHUDDERING]
[GASPS]
[VOICE BREAKING] ♪ Mama's gonna
give you A good-night kiss ♪
Mom?
[SOBS, SNIFFLES]
RAYLAN: Like I said...
everything he told you
was a lie.
[STAMMERS]
JOSEPHINE: My Tara?
[LAUGHS]
You...
got so big, heh.
♪♪♪
Can I hug you?
Come here.
[WHISPERS]
Oh, God.
[CRYING]
Mmm. Oh, God.
Oh, baby, we missed you so much.
JOSEPHINE: Mmm...
There you are.
You were
such a beautiful baby.
[COUGHS]
[WHEEZES, COUGHING]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
- Get it out.
- [COUGHING]
- RAYLAN: Get it out. Come on.
There you go.
There you go. There you go.
- Sorry.
- Nothing to apologize for.
Are you okay?
[JOSEPHINE SIGHS]
The same fire
that destroyed our family...
it burned up my insides.
Mom and Dad used to have a...
kitchen, heh...
in the basement of our house,
where we used to cook.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
It was for our business.
Are you thirsty?
[CHUCKLES]
Tara?
I'm dying.
What?
The smoke from the chemicals...
poisoned my blood
and badly damaged my heart.
I don't think
I have much time left.
Is there anything you can do?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I heard you left flowers for me
at our old house.
Is that true?
Oh.
[SNIFFLES]
Weren't you wishing
your mama
was healthy and alive?
Yes.
I need a new heart, baby.
But not just any heart.
Doctor said
it has to be a, uh...
It must be a...
compatible donor.
Like a direct relative.
You hold the gift
that can save your mama's life.
[CRYING, SNIFFLING]
And, baby, I need that gift.
♪♪♪
[HYPERVENTILATING]
[ECHOING] We'll finally
be together as one.
[WHISPERS]
You'll live on in me.
[GROANING]
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[PANTING]
[WHINES]
Go home.
[BELLS JINGLING FAINTLY]
- [WHINES]
- [SHUSHES]
- [SHUSHES FORCEFULLY]
[BELLS JINGLING]
[GROANS]
♪♪♪
[JINGLING CONTINUES]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[KEYS RATTLE]
[JINGLING]
♪♪♪
[SOBBING]
[DOG WHINES, BARKS]
Go away.
- [WHINING]
- I said, go.
Stay.
♪♪♪
[JINGLES]
Go home.
[BELL JINGLING]
[LIQUID DRIPPING]
[MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY]
[SAW WHIRRING]
[WHIRRING STOPS]
♪♪♪
I hope you understand
the high risks
of this procedure.
RAYLAN: I think I pay you enough.
Shut up and do your job.
Why is she still alive?
SURGEON: If she's dead, so is her heart.
And I can't keep it fresh
long enough
without the proper equipment.
I have to cut it out of her
while she's still breathing.
JOSEPHINE: [WHISPERING] Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
[MOUTHS]
Thank you.
[SIGHS]
JIM-BOB: What's wrong with you, man?
What they're doing
in there is wrong.
She's our cook.
If she dies,
there's no product.
If there's no product,
there's no us.
¿Comprende?
Still fucking wrong.
Hey.
- You ready?
- Mm-hm.
Let's go.
♪♪♪
[WHIRRING]
What the fuck?
Go check it out.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hm.
♪♪♪
[RATS SQUEAKING]
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GUNSHOT]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
You killed my brother!
You blind freak!
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANING]
[BELL JINGLES]
[GROANS]
I'm gonna carve your fucking
head open like a pumpkin, man.
- [GENITALS CRUNCH]
- [YELLING, GAGS]
[GURGLING]
♪♪♪
[GROWLS]
[GAGGING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
[GROANING SOFTLY]
[HAMMER SCRAPES]
This is for Shadow.
Oh, fuck.
[SCREAMS]
No!
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAM ECHOING]
It's him.
♪♪♪
How the hell did he find...?
[BELL JINGLING]
[HUFFS, WHINING]
[YELPS]
Disloyal fucking animal.
JOSEPHINE: Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's okay.
- Everything's okay, I promise.
- Baby, should I be worried?
No, no. Not at all.
I got you. I got you.
I can't work without power.
Uh...
Change of plans, then.
Pack your things.
Bring the girl.
Raul.
Bring the men.
Kill the blind man.
- How many of us?
- All of you!
♪♪♪
Let's go.
[WATER DRIPPING]
♪♪♪
[GASPING]
[COCKS GUN]
[GASPS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
They're gonna kill her.
[CLICKS]
And that's not cool with me.
They're leaving now.
The ladder behind you
leads directly to them.
You'd better hurry.
♪♪♪
RAYLAN: Go left.
That way.
He'll kill you all.
[PHOENIX GROANS]
Fuck it. I'm out.
Hey, hey! Hey!
[BLADE PIERCES FLESH]
[MAN GASPING]
RAYLAN: Good morning, motherfucker.
- JOSEPHINE: [WHISPERS] Baby.
- Shh, shh. It's okay.
- Stop it.
- [GRUNTING]
[METAL CLANGS]
[GAS HISSING]
RAYLAN: Baby?
Hello?
- RAYLAN: I can't see you.
- [COUGHING]
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
[TIRES SQUEAKING]
- Baby?
- [CAN RATTLES]
[CAN EXPLODES]
[GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
- [BLIND MAN GRUNTING]
- [GASPS, THEN GRUNTS]
[CRIES OUT, GROANS]
[COUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
JOSEPHINE: I'm over here! Where are you?
Baby?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
- [CLICKING]
- [BLIND MAN GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
RAYLAN: I got you, motherfucker.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
No.
[SCREAMS]
No! No!
[YELLS]
[CRIES OUT]
[WHIMPERS]
No.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [SHOES SQUEAKING]
- No!
- [MOTOR WHIRRING]
- [PHOENIX GROANING]
[PHOENIX SCREAMS]
♪♪♪
[WHIMPERING]
- [YELLING]
- [BLIND MAN GROANING]
[PHOENIX SCREAMS]
Phoenix!
[DOG BARKING]
[GROWLING]
[GROANS]
[CRIES OUT, PANTING]
[GASPS, THEN YELLING]
[SNARLING]
[DOG BARKING]
- [PANTING]
- [DOG SNARLING, BARKING]
[GASPS]
Now...
you're gonna see
what I see.
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMING]
♪♪♪
[PANTING]
[LIGHT FOOTSTEPS]
Phoenix?
♪♪♪
Stop.
Oh, stop!
You...
You mustn't come near me.
Everything he said...
is true.
I am no father.
I have killed.
I...
have raped.
[SIGHS]
am nothing.
Nothing...
but a monster.
And you...
cannot be around me.
Ever.
So go.
Now. Go.
- Go!
- [GASPS]
♪♪♪
[SIGHS]
[SOBS]
[CRYING]
Oh, God.
- [QUICK FOOTSTEPS]
- [GASPS]
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- [GASPING]
- [BLADE PIERCES AND BLOOD GUSHES]
- [BLIND MAN GASPS]
[BLOOD DRIPPING]
[GROANING SOFTLY]
♪♪♪
Tara?
[WHEEZES]
♪♪♪
[BLIND MAN GROANING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
PHOENIX: No.
[GASPS]
PHOENIX: No. No.
Please.
No, no, no.
Let me help you.
I can save you.
[SOFTLY]
You already have.
[TAKES SHUDDERING BREATH]
[CRYING]
♪♪♪
PHOENIX: Hey.
Hey.
Think there's room for one more?
I'm sure there is.
What's your name?
My name is Phoenix.
♪♪♪
[DOG PANTING, SNIFFING]
[WHINES]
♪♪♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
♪♪♪